A small insistence of my sister brought me to the middle of the
market.  Actually tomorrow
is the second Monday of Sawan and Aafat Ki
Pudiya has to go to visit Lord Shiva after creating a Sawan look.
I explained that
Lord Shiva will not look at your looks but your devotion, but she was not going to
die and brother, she had already
made a list of important things.
I started feeling dizzy after seeing the list and
it took me to a place where even
boys would be dizzy after reaching there.  But somehow I
survived and got her soap items and
brought her home, then she started getting ready quickly.
And what do I see?  So she was
spraying something in her hair like mom.  When
I asked, she told me Bhaiya, I
always
apply Alp Goodness Rosemary Water Spray before combing my hair
because it increases blood circulation in the scalp
and also reduces hair fall three times
and she said, look,
baby Hash has also arrived in 12 weeks.  I quickly
asked how to use it?  It said
spray it on the scalp and massage it gently and
leave it.  And along with this it
is also light weight and non-glittery.  It does
not even feel sticky after application.  I said yes, come on, get
ready quickly now.  Well, if you also
want it then go upstairs and order it.